KANG CHIEN

FULL-STACK & BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

E kangchien1121@gmail.com

A Giallonardo, Benevento, Italy



W http://github.com/prowebdever

ABOUT ME

Full Stack Developer with over 6+years of experience in Windows, Android, , MacOS, etc. and deep knowledge from low to high-level languages. Collaborative Web3 Developer with 4+ years of experience in smart contracts, consensus algorithms, and data structures. Rich experience in implementing of AWS solutions and strong understanding of different development methodologies such as Agile and TDD.

EXPERIENCE

Web3 Developer

Unanet 04/2020-07/2022 Sterling, Virginia, United States

- Hired, trained and lead Agile team of 5 full-stack developers
- Increased company revenue by 30% within 2 months after developing business logic for over 20 features
- Participated in more than 3 projects per year from initial research and conceptual design through testing and implementation phases
- Raised the performance of 17 by a minimum of 36% after using batch processing for file reading
- Saved over 12TB of storage space by creating a PHP script to restrict the host from uploading low quality files or unsupported formats.
- Streamline all offerings with a new responsive, mobile-first approach and strategy which increased mobile traffic by 31%
- Cooperated with the UX designers to create a new look and feel for the website, implemented changes with jQuery library extensions, Ajax & CSS, increasing the time users spend on the website by 40 minutes
- Using solidity framework features, optimized the smart contract program and boosted performance by 18%
- Closely collaborated with the product and dev teams to improve the efficiency of the platform by 19%
- Participated in developing the smart contract, which took me 8 months
- Built 3 reusable cross-chain libraries
- Improved data structures to solve 3 serious issues and ease the work of the dev team

Full Stack Developer

HCL Hong Kong SAR Limited 02/2017-01/2020 Wan Chai, Hong Kong

- Created 40+ technical design documents and implemented business logic for 15 features
- Completed over 300h of training in UX and UI design implementation
- Created a flight schedule search tool for a travel agency
- Integrate internally-developed micro-services, as well as marketplace 3rd party modules
- Designed and developed front-end GUI over 10 applications using JSP, HTML, JavaScript, CSS, and Ajax
- Found and fixed over 70 bugs, increasing security and usability
- Working on the formation and maintenance of innovate blockchain technology, and conducting expert market research
- Gaming platform over Ethereum blockchain using ERC 721

EDUCATION

Hong Kong University of Science and Technology

2012-2016

Clear Water Bay, Hong Kong Bachelor of Computer Science

SKILLS

- HTML & CSS
- **JAVASCRIPT**
- **TYPESCRIPT**
- **PYTHON**
- **IAVA**
- PHP
- **RUBY**
- C, C#, C++
- **REACT JS**
- **ANGULAR**
- NODE IS
- **SPRING**
- **SOLIDITY**
- GO
- **ORACLE**
- **MYSQL**
- **MONGODB**
- **AWS**
- **AZURE**
- **AGILE**

INTERESTING

- **TABLE TENIS**
- **READING BOOK**